Frontend Masters Privacy Policy

This Frontend Masters Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) states the privacy practices and

policies that apply to the Frontend Masters website and software application located at

frontendmasters.com (the “Service”). The Service is owned and operated by MJG International,

LLC (referred to as “Frontend Masters,” “we,” and “our”) and its licensors. This Privacy Policy

applies to all visitors to and registered users (the “user,” “you,” and “your”) of the Service.

Please take the time to read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Accessing and using the Service constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion.

We will provide users and visitors with a notice of such changes posted on the Service itself.

Your continued use of the Service following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy

means that you accept and agree to the changes. This Privacy Policy explains what information

we collect, why we collect it, how we use the information, and your choices for restricting the

use of this information.

Information You Provide Us

We collect personal information directly from you so that you can establish an account and we

can provide the Service to you. This information may include your name, email address, credit

card information and, optionally, your company’s name. We will only use this information to

manage your account and provide you with the Service.

We do not store or process your credit information using our own systems. We contract with

online credit card processing services for all our payment transactions.

When you contact us via email or any other means, we may keep and use a record of that

communication indefinitely to address issues with the Service or for any other business purpose.

We may use your email address to contact you about changes to the Service or this Privacy

Policy.

Information We Collect from Your Use of the Service

We may use the following methods to collect information as you use the Service:

Log Information - When you use the Service we may automatically collect and store certain

information in server logs, such as IP addresses, hardware settings, browser type, and referring

URLs.

Local Storage - We may collect and store information locally on the device you use to access the

Service, such as in web browser storage and application data caches.

Cookies and Other Identifiers - We use various technologies to collect and store information

when you visit the Service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous

identifiers to your device. You may set your web browser to limit or block cookies. If you do so,

the Service may not function properly for you.

We may also compile certain general information related to your use of the Service. You agree

that we are authorized to use, reproduce and generally make such information available to third

parties in the aggregate, provided that your information shall not include personally identifiable

information about you or be attributable to you.

We use all the information that we collect as you use the Service to operate, maintain, protect,

improve, and enhance the Service and your user experience.

Information We Provide to Others

We do not share your personal information with any third parties unless one of the following

applies:

With Account Administrators - If you are using the Service pursuant to a “Master User

Agreement,” as defined in the Frontend Masters User Agreement, then an account administrator

may have access to your account information. This may include your email address, and other

personal information. The person or legal entity with whom we are a party to the Master User

Agreement is responsible for establishing a policy for handling this account information.

Services Vendors --We may provide your personal information to certain vendors that provide

us with services such as network and computer infrastructure, including hosting,

communications, data analytics, advertising and other services. These vendors may only use your

personal information to assist us in providing the Service, subject to appropriate confidentiality

measures.

For Legal Reasons - We may share your personal information with third parties if we determine

that disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: meet any applicable law or

regulation, or comply with any legal process; investigate potential claims and enforce this

Privacy Policy or the Frontend Masters User Agreement; address fraud, security, or technical

issues; or protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of Frontend Masters, our users, or

the public as required or permitted by law.

Upon a Sale of the Business - We may transfer your information to a third party as part of a

merger, reorganization, acquisition, or business asset sale.

How to Access, Correct or Delete Your Information

Send us an email at privacychief@frontendmasters.com if you want to access, review, correct or

delete your personally identifiable information we have collected. To protect your privacy and

security, we may require a user ID and password to verify your identity before granting you the

right to access, review or make corrections to your personally identifiable information. Please be

advised that certain personal information may not be corrected or deleted if we must by law

retain such information as submitted.

Application of this Policy

This Privacy Policy only applies to the Service and this website. It does not apply to any websites

or software applications owned or operated by any third parties, including any websites with

links from our Service. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Service, and to read

the privacy statements of each website that collects personal information from you.

Data Security

Access to your personally identifiable information and all the data you store on the Service is

limited to authorized Frontend Masters personnel and services providers. Although total security

does not exist on the Internet, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard all the

information that you submit us.

Use by Children

The Service is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 18.

Contacting Us

If you have questions or concerns about our practices or this Privacy Policy, please send an email

to: privacychief@frontendmasters.com

Last revised: March 6, 2020.

Copyright 2020 © MJG International, LLC All rights reserved.
